getamap.net 2009-11-07

# Privacy Policy and Confidentiality - Map, Gps, Administration, Flag, Countries, State, Travel, Information.

Privacy Policy and Confidentiality

Getamap.net is committed to safeguarding your privacy online.

When you are on the getamap.net site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information for use by getamap.net alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise.

The transmission of data or information (including communications by e-mail) over the Internet or other publicly accessible networks is not secure, and is subject to possible loss, interception or alteration while in transit. Accordingly, we do not assume any liability for any damage you may experience or costs you may incur as a result of any transmissions over the Internet or other publicly accessible networks, such as transmissions involving the exchange of e-mail with us (including those which may contain your personal information). While we shall take reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of the information you provide us and treat such information in accordance with our Privacy Policy, in no event will the information you provide to us be deemed to be confidential or result in any liability to you on our part in the event that such information is inadvertently released by us or accessed by third parties without our consent.

User Conduct and Obligations

You agree to follow all applicable laws and regulations when using this website. Furthermore, you agree that you shall not:

a. upload, post or otherwise transmit through or to this website any content that: 

i. is unlawful, abusive, threatening, harmful, obscene, lewd, offensive, defamatory or otherwise objectionable; 

ii. might infringe the intellectual property rights, privacy rights, rights of publicity, or other proprietary rights of others; 

iii. contains any viruses, trojan horses, time bombs, or any other harmful programs or elements; 

b. disrupt, place unreasonable burdens or excessive loads on, interfere with or attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion of our website, its computer systems, servers or networks; 

c. transmit junk mail, chain letters, or other unsolicited bulk e-mail or duplicative messages; 

d. collect information about other visitors to our website without their consent or otherwise systematically extract data or data fields, including without limitation any financial data or e-mail addresses; and

e. redistribute any content provided by us in any manner whatsoever.

Proprietary Rights  
Getamap.net and its logo, and other identifying marks of getamap.net are and shall remain the trade-marks and trade names and exclusive property of getamap.net, and any unauthorized use of these marks is unlawful. Other trade-marks on this website are the property of their respective owners. All content on this website is the copyrighted property of getamap.net and is protected by international copyright law. The content on this website may be used by you only for your personal, non-commercial use as provided for in these Terms of Use. Any rights not expressly granted to you are reserved by us. 

Contact

If you have any questions or concerns about our website or these Terms of Use, please feel free to contact us.
